[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question" : "Which IPL team won most number of tropies?",
        "options": [
            "MI",
            "RCB",
            "CSK",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "MI"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question" : "Which IPL Team has lowest Score in IPL",
        "options": [
            "RCB",
            "MI",
            "PKBS",
            "KKR"
        ],
        "answer": "RCB"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question" : "Who is Captain of MI?",
        "options": [
            "MSD",
            "Virat Kolhi",
            "Shikhar Dhawan",
            "Rohit Sharma"
        ],
        "answer": "Rohit Sharma"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question" : "Which player took the only hat trick of IPL 2022??",
        "options": [
            "Harshal Patel",
            "Yuzvendra Chahal",
            "Kuldeep Yadav",
            "Kuldeep Sen"
        ],
        "answer": "Yuzvendra Chahal"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question" : "Who was the most expensive foreign player in IPL 2022 auction?",
        "options": [
            "Liam Livingstone",
            "Pat Cummins",
            "Jofra Archer",
            "Shimron Hetmyer"
        ],
        "answer": "Liam Livingstone"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question" : "Who was the Man of the Match in the IPL 2022 final?",
        "options": [
            "Rashid Khan",
            "Shubman Gill",
            "Hardik Pandya",
            "David Miller"
        ],
        "answer": "Hardik Pandya"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question" : "Who Won the IPL 2022?",
        "options": [
            "GT",
            "CSK",
            "MI",
            "RCB"
        ],
        "answer": "GT"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question" : "Who recorded the highest individual score in IPL?",
        "options": [
            "KL Rahul",
            "Chris Gayle",
            "Rohit Sharma",
            "Virat Kolhi"
        ],
        "answer": "Chris Gayle"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question" : " Which two teams lost the most games in IPL 2022?",
        "options": [
            "MI,CSK",
            "GT,RR",
            "SRH,PKBS",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "MI,CSK"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question" : "Who is RCB's Captain curently",
        "options": [
            "Virat Kolhi",
            "Faf",
            "Harshal Patel",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "Faf"
    }
]